question_data =  [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
        },
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                           "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                           "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
